ANDREW OMONDI OCHIENG

Contact Information

Address: Nandi, Kenya

Email: andrewomosh44@gmail.com

Phone: +254 710815080

Github: https://github.com/AndrewMartial

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-ochieng-00b076180/

Portfolio: https://andrew-oochieng.netlify.app/

Personal Statement

Analytical, solution-oriented and detailed Web frontend developer professional with stellar communication skills. Adept at bringing all team members together to reach a common goal on time and under budget. Conceptualizing web solutions with the latest technology, design theory, and a large dose of creativity. Committed to viable and easily functional web solutions for clients.

Highlighted Software Applications

Kakamega CSO Network - Web Developer, Web Software Engineer April 2022

URL: https://www.kakamegacsonetwork.org/

Kakamega CSO Network Website is a platform that informs the public, donors and interested persons of the key functions of the network. The site further displays events that the network has or may undertake in the future. Further, there's a news platform where one can find all the latest occurrences of the network

Finally, the site has all the contact details with an inclusion of a google map for easier communication and reach of the network's officials.

Technical Skills

Strong: HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Bootstrap5, Wordpress, Javascript

Experience: Python, SQL CSS3, Javascript, Vuejs js, firebase.

Personal Skills

- Passionate software developer with problem-solving skills.
- Teamwork worked with collaboration tools for example git, .
- Strong communication skills and works well under minimal supervision.
- Adaptable to changes

Employment History

- Intern, Junior Software Developer, Taquana Limited
 - May 2022 August 2022
- Web Developer, Kakamega CSO Network,
 - April 2022 May 2022
- Frontend Web Developer, Vabrise Technologies,
 - March 2021 April 2022
- Graphics Designer, Vabrise Technologies
 - March 2021 April 2022

Achievements and Responsibilities:

- Worked with a team of three in developing Taquana's Nganya Webapp. A webapp that enables end users to book matatu online.
- Lead a team of three developers in developing the Kakamega CSO Network website. A website that enables the public to understand in detail the operations of the organization.

Academic Qualification

Zuri Training Program,

May 2022 - Present,

Frontend Software Development.

University of Eastern Africa, Baraton,

September 2017 - August 2021,

Bachelor of Science in Education.

Nyakhobi Secondary School,

2013 - 2016,

Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education.

Interests

- Reading tech blogs.
- Biking.
- Languages: English(fluent), Swahili(fluent).

References

References will be provided upon request.